[
   {
    "level": 1,
    "name":"levelone",
    "questions":[
       { "question":"a citrus fruit that is round and that has an orange skin"},
       { "question":"a usually round object that is used in a game or sport or as a toy"},
       { "question":"the clear liquid that has no color, taste, or smell, that falls from clouds as rain, that forms streams, lakes, and seas, and that is used for drinking, washing, etc."},
       { "question":"a large natural flow of water that crosses an area of land and goes into an ocean, a lake, etc."},
       { "question":"a thick growth of trees and bushes that covers a large area"}
    ],
    "answers":[
        {"answer":"orange"},
        {"answer":"ball"},
        {"answer":"water"},
        {"answer":"river"},
        {"answer":"forest"}
    ]
   } ,
   {
    "level": 2,
    "name":"leveltwo",
    "questions":[
       { "question":"an area of land that rises very high above the land around it and that is higher than a hill"},
       { "question":"a large wild animal that has four long thin legs, brown fur, and antlers if male"},
       { "question":"a hard usually transparent material that is used for making windows and other products"},
       { "question":"a device that is used to open a lock or start an automobileThe usual type of key is a small metal object that you insert into a narrow opening and turn."},
       { "question":"a device that is used for protection from the rain and sun,An umbrella consists of a circle of fabric attached to a folding frame that is connected to a central pole or handle."}
    ],
    "answers":[
        {"answer":"mountain"},
        {"answer":"deer"},
        {"answer":"glass"},
        {"answer":"key"},
        {"answer":"umbrella"}
    ]
   }
]